https://miwf.org/privacy-policy/

UGOGirlsforChange
Virtual – S.T.E.A.M.
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for
MIWF.org. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this
website. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you
through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your
information.How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on
this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give
us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this
information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding
the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third
party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your
request.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in
the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to
this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any
time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email
address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any. Change/correct any data we have about you. Have us delete any data we have about you. Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you
submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected
both online and offline.
If we collect sensitive information (such as credit card
data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You
can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for
“https” at the beginning of the address of the Web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information
transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees
who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or
customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information.
The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are
kept in a secure environment.
Cookies
We use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data
stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our
site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a
cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once,
thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and
target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage
of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on
our site.
Links
This website contains links to other sites. Please be
aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such
other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to
read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally
identifiable information.
Surveys & Contests
From time-to-time our site requests information via
surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely
voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore
disclose this information. Information requested may include contact
information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information
(such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the
winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring
or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.
If
you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us
immediately via email at ptallet@miwf.org or
telephone at 313-771-3513.
Detroit Office 1155 Brewery Park Blvd.
Suite 350
Detroit, MI 48207
Phone: 313.962.1920
Fax: 313.962.1926
Lansing Office 105 W. Allegan St.
Virtual – S.T.E.A.M.
